Hanger kouka (a Japanese word meaning "hanger rack")
Hi, I'm Mr. Hanger, born in the conference room of Starlast and raised on a hanger rack!
Here I am!
Now, let's call today's guest!
This is my idol.
Mr. Kou from Ukka, right?
Repairman Muraho.
Pleased to meet you.
I heard that Ukka has just released her first major single
Wonder Little Love.
Yes, that's right.
There are three songs in the album, Wonder Little Love, Tailwind and Graph Days.
Wonder Little Love has a music video and a dance performance video.
Please take a look at the music video and dance performance video for Wonder Little Love.
Thank you very much.
Wonder Little Love, our first major single
Oricon Weekly Ranking No. 5.
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
Weekly is No. 5 and Ravey is No. 3, so
We were taken by many people and
We were able to make it to the top of the list.We were able to make it to the top of the list!
Thank you very much.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
And may I ask about the relationship between Mr. Kabase and Osamu Muraho?
Yes, our relationship started in 2015
That's right, extra.
Yes, I do, but...
We've been together for about 89 years now.
That's a long relationship.
Yes, we have.
We are, you know, we are called Blue Babe.
I'm a blue bebe, and I'm a yellow bebe, so...
I'm pretty much on my own, you know, because I often go on campaigns.
I go on the radio and so on.
So when I do, I get along well with the Blue Babe duo.
We really have a lot of fun together.
Bulbabebe
Well, I think that's a good name for a duo.
Well, here we are.
I'd like to ask you two to present your plans for worship.
May I ask you to do it?
Yes, please.
Hangatou, Ukka.
I'll start with the card.Okay, I'll start with the card.
Please.
1. Starbucks
2. perfume
3. delivery
Starbucks, perfume, delivery.
Okay, one at a time, one at a time?
Yes.
1. Starbucks. I really love Starbucks.
Yes, you drink your favorite drink every day.
I drink as much as you do.
Last summer I was addicted to black tea,
I drank black tea every day,
This year, I had an iced matcha tea latte.
I've become a leeker.
Oh, wow.
That's amazing.
That's the type of thing I'm talking about.
It's a matcha reaction.
So this summer, I'm going to drink matcha tea lattes.
I would like to spend it.
I've never had a Starbucks for a fan,
Can you tell me what you would recommend to a newcomer?
Do you like coffee, Mr. Hunker?
I can drink a little coffee every now and then.I thought I could drink a little bit of coffee.
I can drink a little bit at a time.
I see.
If that's the case, then Starbucks Coffee,
There is something called Starbucks Latte,
That's pretty much the standard coffee.
I think that's about it.
I'm not recommending middle school, but middle school.
But the cash register, too. I don't really touch it.
Right, so vanilla and so on.
But I had one recently, like a strawberry Frappuccino.
I thought it was really good, so I thought I'd like to have it again.
Let's go have a drink.
I want to go.
Next number two, perfume.
Perfume.
Perfume?
Not perfume.
I know perfume.
Perfume, yes, I know perfume, but how do you like perfume?
Perfume. I really love the smell,
When I'm with someone who seems to smell good, and when I'm not,
I breathe it all out in that direction, and in that moment, I go, ahhh, I love the way it smells.
Yes, but when I like it best, the perfume is,
Recently, I've been wearing Insirona's Onmpa,Lately, I've been wearing Insirona's Onnipa,
It smells good, doesn't it? Do you have a Riza?
I do. I have one too.
It smells so good, and the smell is so strong that you can't take it off even if you take a bath after putting it on.
Is it that strong?
I've never put it on every year,
Please wear it in the summer and smell good.
Well then, take a lesson from Mr. Perfume's perfume and smell good, too,
I think I will ask Mr. Perfume to put on perfume,
Next, number 3, what is it?
Delivery!
Delivery.
That's right.
Lately, I've been doing almost daily TV staff communication and fan club distribution,
I'm sure everyone listens to the staff comic,
I also do a lot of fan club broadcasts,
The fan club distribution is really fast.
That's right. The fan club is very fast.
Why, I'm just going to talk in circles,
You know, there are times when we talk in a roundabout way.
I know, I know. I talk while being careful.
I notice that time goes by.
That's right. Really.
You can't see it.
I have an image of you as being long-winded.I have a long image.
Yes. I am very much.
Yes.
So, in my mind, the staff is probably made to deliver perfume.
When I heard about the delivery, I thought, "Well, I don't know,
I have taken in the information that Perfume was No. 1 in the delivery time of Kamihanky on the staff forum,
How was it?
It seems so,
That's great. That's great.
I've got time. It's not great.
But it's a lot of distribution, and I think the fans are happy.
But I only do it 9 times a month. Me.
Nine times?
I only do it about nine times.
But the more I do it, the better I feel.
I was thinking earlier that I haven't been able to do it at all,
So...
I'll do it.
Please do it.
I'm going to be number one in nine.
How many hours?
Maybe 3...
I've been at it for 34 hours total,
Each session is 1.5 to 2 hours,
So it's an accumulation.So it's a stack, right?
Maybe so.
Then that's great.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
I've been reading your staff comic, Perfume-san,
I would like to ask you to check out the staff comm. of Perfume and Ukauka.
Hanga and Ukauka
Well, that's all for now. We have heard a lot of stories from you two,
Can I make a final announcement?
Yes. We, Uka, are going to have a one-man live concert in Japan this year.
First, on September 30 at BEATS Shibuya, and then on October 14 at Tokyo Kinema Group,
We hope you will come and see us.
Please come and join us.
I hope you will come and enjoy the live performance.
Lastly, I would like to introduce myself as Mr. Hunker,
I'd like to ask you to catch him on camera,
I would like to ask you to take a message at the end of this presentation.
Okay.
I'm Hamburger, after all.
Thank you very much.
Finally.
Sad.
To the camera.
Shall we say bye-bye with a message?Shall we say bye-bye by message?
Okay, that's it.
That was Uka.
Bye-bye and come back for fun!
Thank you very much.
This program is a part of
Mt. Fuji
Mr. Hikiniku
Nomu Nomu Leader
Courtesy of Kokorotan